strexm.tv 2018-06-25

# Strexm - Privacy Policy

### OVERVIEW

Strexm ("Strexm", "us", "we", "our") are committed to safeguarding your privacy. In this Privacy Policy we explain what personal information we collect, how we collect this information, and how we may share this information.

By using our web site and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy.

* * *

### INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT

A visitor using our web site, without connecting to the service, is not required to provide any personal information, except in the case of contacting us.

As a user, we may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your computer and visits to and use of this web site (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and web site navigation paths);
  * information that you provide to us when connecting to our service (including your Twitch username, Twitch avatar and your email address);
  * information that you provide to us when using the services on our web site, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services;
  * information contained in or relating to any communications that you send to us or send through our web site (including the communication content and meta data associated with the communication);
  * any other personal information that you choose to send to us.

### HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Personal information submitted to us through our web site will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the web site.

We may use your personal information to:

  * personalise our service for you;
  * enable your use of the services on our web site;
  * send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from you;
  * contact you;
  * provide personal, customer support;
  * verify your identity and prevent fraud;
  * send marketing and promotional material;
  * notify you of important service updates.

### DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will not sell, rent, or supply your personal information to any third party for the purpose of their or any other third party's marketing.

We may disclose your personal information:

  * to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  * in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings;
  * in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights;
  * to any of our employees, subcontractors, or external services (including payment processors) as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this policy.

### RETAINING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes.

### SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We store all personal information on our secure, password and firewall protected servers.

You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are solely responsible for the safety of your account. We will never ask for your password except for when you log into our web site. This login process is provided by an external service (e.g. Twitch) and we will never see your password.

### DATA GATHERING

We retain the right to collect from you non personal identifying information collected from your use of our service and gather such data for internal analytics.

### COOKIES

Our web site uses cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server.

Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.

Some cookies used on this site may store your personal information within. This personal information is encrypted using 256bit AES.

We use both session and persistent cookies on our web site.

The names of the cookies that we use on our web site, and the purposes for which they are used, are set out below:

  * we use "ci_session" on our web site to personalise the web site for each user and to allow the user to access his or her specific service. **This cookie is persistent and will not be deleted until you specifically logout.**
  * we use "csrf_token" on our web site to protect users from cross-site request forgery attacks. More information on these types of attacks can be found [here](https://www.owasp.org/index.php/Cross-Site_Request_Forgery_%28CSRF%29). **This cookie is persistent and will not be deleted.**
  * we use "_ga" on our web site to distinguish users for analytical purposes.
  * we use "_gat" on our web site to throttle the request rate of analytical purposes.

Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many web sites, including the one in which you are using right now.

If you block cookies, you will not be able to use the service or features on this web site.

You can delete cookies already stored on your computer; for example:

  * in Internet Explorer (version 10), you must manually delete cookie files (you can find instructions for doing so at http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835);
  * in Firefox (version 37), you can delete cookies by accessing the "Open menu" menu, and clicking "Options", "Privacy", and then selecting "Remove individual cookies", and then clicking "Remove All Cookies"; and
  * in Chrome (version 41), you can delete all cookies by accessing the "Customise and control" menu, and clicking "Settings", "Show advanced settings" and "Clear browsing data", and then selecting "Delete cookies and other site and plug-in data" before clicking "Clear browsing data".

Deleting cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many web sites, including the one in which you are using right now.

### THIRD PARTY WEB SITES

Our web site includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party web sites. We hold no control over, and not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties. Your access to such linked web sites is at your own risk.

### CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

As we continue to develop, we may change or add new services or features to our web site. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. Please check back regularly for any amendments. The latest update date can be found at the end of this policy.

### DETAILS AND CONTACT

This web site is owned and operated by SplitmediaLabs Limited, a company incorporated in Hong Kong. You may contact us directly through one of the means listed on our [contact page](https://strexm.tv/contact).

* * *

Last Updated: 28th February 2016
